Another Steven Soderbergh Experience
Bubble is a drama, crime, mystery film directed by Steven Soderbergh.
Set against the backdrop of a decaying Midwestern town, a murder becomes
the focal point of three people who work in a doll factory.
Martha, played by Debbie Doebereiner.
Martha's Father, played by Omar Cowan.
Kyle (as Dustin Ashley), played by Dustin James Ashley.
Bakery Shopkeeper, played by Phyllis Workman.
Kyle's Mother (as Laurie Lee), played by Laurie L. Wee.
Factory Supervisor, played by Daniel R. Christian.
The Bubble (Hebrew: הבועה, romanized: HaBuah) is a 2006 romantic drama directed by Eytan Fox
telling the story of two men who fall in love, one Israeli and one Palestinian.
The title of the film is the nickname of Tel Aviv for it being a
relatively peaceful city, remote from the war actions.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.